typeandgrids.com 2018-12-19

# Type & Grids — Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Type & Grids is owned and operated by [Jeremiah Shoaf Design LLC](http://www.jeremiahshoaf.com/).

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

Note: The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you follow links to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

#### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Type & Grids website. On our home page you can submit your email address to sign up for product updates. The types of personal information collected in this form are the following:

Email address

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Type & Grids may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Type & Grids sole discretion. Type & Grids encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy.

#### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please email us at:

Our mailing address is:  
Jeremiah Shoaf Design LLC  
PO Box 746524  
Arvada, CO 80006-6524  

#### Disclosure

Some of the external links on Type & Grids are affiliate links. If a visitor clicks a link and makes a purchase, Type & Grids may receive a commission.
